[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before making the change to a decimal based monetary system, one English guinea was comprised of this many shillings.  Coincidentally, it is also the number of letters in the Italian alphabet.", "correct_answer": "21", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "18", "29"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This horror film, based on a Stephen King novel, revolves around a group of people who seek revenge against a ghostly clown.", "correct_answer": "It", "incorrect_answers": ["Misery", "The Langoliers", "Sometimes They Come Back for More"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How were women referred to in New York City of 2022 in Soylent Green?", "correct_answer": "Furniture", "incorrect_answers": ["Toys", "Playmates", "Home-stations"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous novel begins with the sentence: Whether I shall turn out to be the hero of my own life, or whether that station will be held by anybody else, these pages must show.?", "correct_answer": "David Copperfield", "incorrect_answers": ["Great Expectations", "The Last of the Mohicans", "The Old Man and the Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many subspecies of the tiger are left nowadays?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "2", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor was initially offered the role of Neo in the 1999 movie The Matrix?", "correct_answer": "Will Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Denzel Washington", "Cuba Gooding, Jr.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The nutria is a herbivorous animal.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Woody Allen romantic comedy film, starring Diane Keaton and Woody Allen himself, won four Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Annie Hall", "incorrect_answers": ["Hannah and Her Sisters", "Mighty Aphrodite", "Manhattan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many US states border the Pacific Ocean?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["11", "4", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What chemical present in the grapefruit gives it its unique taste and flavor?", "correct_answer": "Sulfur", "incorrect_answers": ["Nitrogen", "Vanadium", "Formaldehyde"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the capital and largest city of Norway?", "correct_answer": "Oslo", "incorrect_answers": ["Reykjavik", "Bergen", "Helsinki"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What system of the human body provides a site for blood cell formation?", "correct_answer": "Skeletal", "incorrect_answers": ["Cardiovascular", "Integumentary", "Endocrine"]}]